<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf8'?>
<sbtp>
  <group prefix="promo_blackfriday_">
    <item suffix="3_dlg_accept_1_gil">Hot dog! You won’t regret this! I promise!</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_accept_2_gil">…That’s not a legally binding guarantee by the way.</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_decline_1_gil">Well, if you change your mind you can find the deal in the premium item menu.</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_decline_2_gil">Although I don't get paid a commission when you buy it that way.</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_1_gil">Hey, has Ol' Gil got a Black Friday sale for you!</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_2_gil">You probably don’t need it, or even want it -- heck, it may not even be that good of deal.</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_3_gil">But it’s Black Friday, so you'll think it is.  And you'll buy it!</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_4_gil">Please buy it.</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_5_gil">But hey, at least you’ll always have that toaster and every time you see it… *Sob*</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_6_gil">Anyway, has Gil got a Black Friday deal for you!</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_7_gil">You probably don’t need it, or even want it, but it’s Black Friday, so you have to buy it…</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_8_gil">Gil bought that toaster on credit Gil doesn’t have!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Here’s some stuff that has nothing to do with Thanksgiving but you definitely want to buy anyway!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Including Duffman, Duff Brewery, Springfield Sign, and $50,000!</item>
    <item suffix="infotext">A new item offer every hour! Check back often!</item>
    <item suffix="speechbubble">Buy limited time sale items and get donut rebates right on the spot!</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_breweryandsign_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_homer">Is the Duff supply safe?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_duffman">Oh yea!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_3_homer">Thank you giant Sky Finger, you’ve saved our Springfield!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Can’t get enough Duff? Brew more today!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Jumpstart your Springfield with: </item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_homer">Hey. HEY! Yes, you! The Sky finger.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_2_homer">If you let this town run out of Duff, you’ll be sorry!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_3_lisa">There’s probably enough Duff stockpiled to last any normal city a 50 years!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_4_homer">But what about Springfield!?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">You sir, do you enjoy a Duff?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_homer">Well, I have been known to enjoy a celebratory glass on occasion.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_gil">Did you realize that no one is brewing it anymore in Springfield? We could run out at any time!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_homer">Ahh-hh!</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_broadcastdishplusburningbush_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_gil">It worked. It actually worked. You bought something!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_gil">This happens less than 2% of the time!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Improve your reception with a huge broadcast dish! </item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">“Unlock a new Broadcast Job for Channel 6!”</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_3_misc">“Bonus: Burning bush, set on fire by microwaves!”</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_4_misc">50 Donut Value!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">*sigh* I really felt that one getting away from me.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Oh man, how am I supposed to pitch a Broadcast Dish and a burning bush?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_gil">Umm, how about—</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_homer">Can we get satellite radio with that dish?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_gil">Umm, sure! Why not?</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_buildmenutag_">
    <item suffix="nogil">Special Offer!</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_dayolddonuts_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_gil">Really? Well hot damn! The kids are going to eat tonight!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Day Old Donuts! They don't taste as good, but they purchase premium content just fine.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Donuts Up to 25% Off!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_3_misc">25% More Donuts!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">C'mon, Gil really needs this. They're going to take my kidney!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Ol' Gil's got a real sweet treat for you today, Springfield.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_gil">Day Old Donuts!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_homer">Mmm… donuts.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_lisa">You're not really planning to eat those stale donuts, are you?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_5_homer">No, I'm going to use them to purchase Professor Frink, have him build a time machine, then travel back in time to when the donuts were still fresh.  And then eat them.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_duffbreweryplusspringfieldsign_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_homer">I'm sorry I said all those mean things about you, Gil.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_gil">Aw, it's fine. Maybe you can buy me a Duff next time I come back.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_3_homer">Don't come back.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Get the Duff Brewery, complete with its manic corporate shill, Duffman!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Including $50,000, Springfield Sign, Duffman and Duff Brewery!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">Well, if you change your mind you can find the deal in your premium item menu.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_2_gil">Although I don't get paid a commission when you buy it that way.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Okay, Gil. Just like you rehearsed.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_gil">Excuse me, fine sir--</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_homer">No, not you again! You're the most annoying thing in this town!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_homer">You know everyone hates you, right?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_5_gil">They do? Why?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_6_homer">Because you're an ad. We're people, who do funny things and earn money. But you're just an ad.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_7_gil">Aw, jeez. I'm just trying to pay for my kid's braces… the walking kind, not the teeth kind. </item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_8_homer">Ugh, fine. But whatever you're selling, I'm not interested.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_9_gil">The Duff Brewery, complete with Duffman.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_10_homer">Really?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_11_homer">Gil, you're the greatest! I love you, I love you, I love you…</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_frinklabplusbuddha_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_frink">Let's hear it for science, mm-hai!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_kearney">Shut up, nerd!  *punch*</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Who wouldn't want an awkward nerd in their town?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">And get all this other stuff!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_3_misc">Including: Frink’s Lab, Professor Frink, $50 000 and Homer Buddha.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_4_misc">490 Donut Value!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_frink">It’s that kind of disinterest in science that's keeping us from going to Mars!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Scientists! Get your scientists here!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_lisa">You can't sell the creation of a scientist!  Only graduate schools can do that.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_frink">Please little girl, I've been trapped alone for so long in a plane of existence that only I understand.  I just want to come back and be  trapped alone in my laboratory.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_icecreamman_">
    <item suffix="title">Ice Cream Truck</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_lairsign_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_hankscorpio">That's good work, Gil.  Now to enslave the human race and make you all work in my mines.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_gil">Oh boy, a job!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Nothing says, “I’m in charge” like a giant super laser!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Including: Volcano Lair, evil super genius Hank Scorpio and Springfield Sign.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_3_misc">370 Donut Value! </item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">Come on!  Don't you want to protect your town from those Columbians?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Heya Springfield!  Are you tired of “the man” telling you what to do?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_homer">Which man?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_gil">The man in Washington!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_homer">Which Washington?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_5_gil">Well, now you can stand up to our government by scrawling your city name across a mountain and protecting it with a death ray!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_6_homer">Cause there's Washington state and the District of Columbia… which is kind of weird.  Isn't Columbia another country?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_7_gil">Yeah, that is weird.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_newsvanandmysterybox_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_kentbrockman">This just in, annoying sales person Gil Gunderson WAS NOT beaten to a pulp by angry loan sharks. Now this reporter has seen it all.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Free Mystery Box with every News Van!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">46 Donut Value!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">Oh, who am I kidding? There was probably only a shrub in that box. I mean it could have been a been something really cool, but what are the chances of that?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">You there, you look like you could use a Channel 6 News Van!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_homer">Why the hell would we want that?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_gil">Umm, because I’ll throw in what’s ever is in this Mystery Box!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_homer">Mystery Boxes, my Chilli’s heel.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_5_lisa">Dad, I think you mean Achilles’ heel.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_6_homer">Chilli… *drools*</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_observatoryplustireyard_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_gil">Really? You want it? Hot damn!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_homer">Yep, that’s right. And it’ll cost you if you want to keep warming yourself at MY tire fire.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_3_gil">Ow, What have I done?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Keep warm while stargazing with the warm glow of burning tires.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Includes the Tire Yard and Springfield Observatory!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_3_misc">115 Donut Value!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">Aw, common Homer. Don’t let your little girl down -- don’t be like Gil.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_2_lisa">I’m OK actually. The tire fire would have been terrible for the environment.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_3_gil">You’re such a brave little environmentalist.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_4_homer">Environmentalist? NOOOO!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Have you ever wonder what lies beyond the heavens?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_homer">No, not really.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_lisa">But I have!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_gil">Hrm. Think quickly Gil, you’re almost there.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_5_gil">Homer, have you ever warmed yourself by a burning tire on a cold night?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_6_homer">On occasion.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_7_gil">Well then I’ve got a deal for the both of you! …I hope.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_ottobusandcash_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_gil">Oh boy, I didn’t think I had any chance of selling that. What with the smell!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_otto">Ugh, not so loud man.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">For Sale: One slightly crashed school bus with slightly used driver included!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Also has $5000 stashed in the seats.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_3_misc">160 Donut Value!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">I can’t say I blame you. Otto’d probably just hang out on your coach all day, and eat everything in your fridge. Hey, maybe you’d buy me instead?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">For sale: One slightly crashed school bus with $5000 cash back!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_lisa">What’s that smell?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_otto">Uh, my head.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_gil">Oh. For Sale: One slightly crashed school bus, with $5000 cash back! Driver included.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_premiumdecorations_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_gil">You bought something?  Man, I can't wait to tell the guys at the shelter!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_gil">But don’t stop there, I could really use a home run with this one.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Premium Decorations -- they look as great as they earn bonus money!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Up to 30% Off!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">Aw, come on.  Not even a white picket segment?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_2_gil">I could really use the commission.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Is your town a little down?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_gil">Could you use a fancy new bench, fruit tree or Tire Fire?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_gil">For some reason that makes no sense, having them in your town lets you earn more money!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_gil">You gotta spend money to make money 

-- real money to make fake money!</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_promokrustylu_">
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_1_gil">Fans of Krusty, have I got a treat for you!</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_2_gil">Get the studio where his show is recorded, as well as his side-kick Sideshow Mel and a cannon to shoot him from! </item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_3_homer">Can I get Krusty too?</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_4_gil">Umm, no. He's a regular character. You probably already have him. </item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_5_homer">Oh, right. He does that thing with the giant exclamation point -- I remember now. </item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_6_homer">Well, can I have some other premium character? Like a random one that has nothing to do with Krusty or his studios? </item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_7_gil">But that wouldn't make any sense.</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_8_homer">I'm walking away…</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_9_gil">Okay, okay!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_3_dlg_accept_1_sideshowmel">Egad! Where are you planning to shoot me with that cannon?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_3_dlg_accept_2_drnick">High, everybody!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_3_dlg_decline_1_gil">No problem. There's still plenty of cheese on the inside of that pizza box I found earlier.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Get the Krusty Premium package… for some reason with Dr. Nick!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_misc">Includes Krustylu Studios, Sideshow Mel, a Cannon and the “Doctor”.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_santasvillageplusxmastree_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_gil">Honey, I made a sale!  Tell the kids I'll be home for Christmas!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_gil">What do you mean I'm not welcome?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_3_gil">You got remarried already?!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Celebrate consumerism with this holiday inspired theme park and tree!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">275 Donut Value!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_3_misc">Including: Santa’s Village, Holiday Tree and Santa Homer!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">Hi, honey? I need you to tell the kids Christmas is cancelled again this year.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_2_gil_cut">Is that a man’s voice I hear?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_3_gil_cut">What? No… come on, it’s Christmas. I even have money this year.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Ho-ho-ho, just wait until you see what I’ve got for you today.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_lisa">Is it a pony?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_homer">Is it a large screen TV?  'Cause I could stop breaking in to the Brown House if I had one of those.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_secondtap_">
    <item suffix="dlg_1_gil">Oh boy, oh boy, you're back! Come on Gil, don't screw this up again.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_2_gil">Saw something that caught your eye, eh? Please don't leave again.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_3_gil">Please buy something this time. I'm going to lose my kids!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_4_gil">A second chance? Oh thank you, thank you, thank you.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_5_gil">Your back? Your back! I can't hardly believe it.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_6_gil">Alright Gil. You can maybe do it this time.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_7_gil">Oh god, please let me sell something this time.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_8_gil">You have no idea how much I need this.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_9_gil">Please buy something, I can't sell anymore blood. Uwooh…</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_10_gil">WELcoME. I'VE lost CONtrol of my vOICe tAKING experiMENTAL DRUGS!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_11_gil">Come on, doesn't Gil get a lick?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_12_gil">Help Gil out. I don't have the back to be a cat burglar.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_13_gil">Oh wow! A customer!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_14_gil">Don't mind the bleeding, I was just with my bookie.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_15_gil">C'mon, help ol'Gil out here!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_16_gil">Take a look… please! I can't afford another divorce.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_17_gil">Just one more sale and I'll finally have that hot plate paid for.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_18_gil">If you won't buy something, can you at least push me in front of an expensive looking car?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_19_gil">Don't get my hopes up, I can't take another rejection.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_20_gil">I'm just trying to earn enough money to buy my real eyes back.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_21_gil">Alright Gil, remember… ABCD: Always Be Closing Donuts!</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_soccercup_">
    <item suffix="text">Try Lady Duff today! She's mean, she's lean… she's the beer queen. OH YEAH!</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_svtplusmysterybox_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_svt">That part about me not getting paid wasn’t true, right?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Squeaky Voice Teen works for you, but you get to keep money!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_svt">Heeey!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_3_misc">You’ll also get his belongings: Mystery Box, 25 Donuts, $5000</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_4_misc">You’ll also get his belongings:</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_5_misc">Mystery Box, 25 Donuts, $5000</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_6_svt">Squeaky Voice Teen works for you, but you get to keep money!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">How can you deny that oily, pimply face a thankless life in your Springfield?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Got a crummy job that no grown person would be willing to do? Well, then get yourself a teen!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_lisa">A handsome teenaged boy, who's smart but misunderstood because he plays by his own rules? </item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_gil">No, a Squeaky-Voiced Teen.  He's none of those things!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_homer">Phew.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_theatrebuddhaandlardlads_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_gil">Yippie! A sale!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_gil">Kids, we’re going to go see a movie, and daddy will even buy you each a donut!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_3_gil">What do your mother said I’m not supposed to call you!?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">What’s better than donuts and a movie?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">205 Donut Value!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_homer">Where’s my movie and donuts? I’m holding you responsible Gil!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_2_gil">Oh boy.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Springfield, maybe you’d like to get a few new buildings?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_homer">Pssh! That sounds like work.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_gil">No no, come back! Make the sky finger do all the work. Then you can catch a movie, or eat donuts whenever you want.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_homer">You heard him Sky finger. Don’t let me down.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_thespiritofgiving_">
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_homer">Mmm… extra donuts.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_2_lisa">Should we set some out for Santa?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_3_homer">No way!  The only fat guy getting his hands on these is me.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_1_gil">Celebrate the season with even more donuts!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_art_2_misc">Get 25% More Donuts with every Pack!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">Ah, jeez!  Guess the kids will have to go the another Christmas without presents… or electricity.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_2_gil">If I can’t sell donuts in Springfield, I’m ruined!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_1_gil">Ho-ho-ho boy.  Have I got a Christmas miracle for you!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_2_gil">To celebrate the season, all donut packages come with 25% more donuts!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_3_gil">Which means a dozen is now 15.  50 is the new 40!  And that tray of 132 donuts is now… well, Ol Gil's not that good at math.  If he was, he wouldn't have to be standing out here in the cold hawking donuts.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_gil">He's also not that good at grammar, always calling himself he instead of I…</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_4_homer">Do you know how many jobs the sky finger has made me do this year!?</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_5_homer">Fine, I'll look at the store.  Just shut up already!</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_start_6_homer">Bless you, fat sir.</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_xmas2013_">
    <item suffix="gilbubble">Holiday donuts… Get 'em while they are still appropriate to the season!</item>
  </group>
  <group prefix="promo_xmas2013holidaydonuts_">
    <item suffix="1_name">Holidays 2013 Donut Bonus</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_1_gil">Holiday donuts! Get your holiday donuts! Available exclusively here from ol' Gil!</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_2_homer">Gil?! You're the guy who snapped up all those holiday donuts?</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_3_gil">Yup! And I've got so many of them I'll be selling them for months… at an inflated price, of course!</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_4_homer">Months? But no one is going to want to buy holiday donuts after Christmas.</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_5_gil">Oh, I didn't think of that. Gil's really stepped in it this time. Do you think my donut surplus will hold until next year?</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_6_homer">Nobody's going to buy year-old donuts, Gil. Also, who's going to still be playing this game in a year?</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_7_gil">Oh God, you're right. I need to sell my entire supply before the bottom falls out of the market. I have to cut my price, take a loss… how about bonus donuts with every purchase?</item>
    <item suffix="3_dlg_start_8_homer">*snickers* It's the Hunt brothers all over again.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_accept_1_gil">Every sale I make is a loss! Even when you buy my stuff, you're killing ol' Gil here.</item>
    <item suffix="dlg_decline_1_gil">Aw jeez, I really need this. It will determine what level of bankruptcy I have to file after the holidays.</item>
  </group>
</sbtp>