<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf8'?>
<sbtp>
  <group prefix="push_">
    <item suffix="aroundtheworld_act3hasstarted">Come back and win Norbert Van Houten and his Plane!</item>
    <item suffix="aroundtheworld_maxvisitors">Your town is full of Visitors! Time to collect their tributes!</item>
    <item suffix="aroundtheworld_maxvisitors24h">The Tourists are ready! Come back and tap them!</item>
    <item suffix="aroundtheworld_newnorberttasks">Norbert has new Adventure Tasks available!</item>
    <item suffix="build_complete">Woo-hoo! New Building!</item>
    <item suffix="build_complete_alt">{0} has finished building.</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_androidsdungeon">Android's Dungeon has been built and Comic Book Guy is back. "Worst. Apocalypse. Ever."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_bartstreehouse">Bart's Treehouse has been built and Bart is back. "I, for one, would like to be the first to say… I didn't do it."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_character1">{0} has been built and {1} is back. "It's about time someone added me to this game!"</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_character2">{0} has been built and {1} is back. "Did you miss me?"</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_character3">{0} has been built and {1} is back. "Whew! It's good to be back. I owe you one!"</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_cletusfarm">Cletus' Farm has been built and Cletus is back. "First day back and I already got me a prime piece of dirt where I can get my squat on!"</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_eatery1">{0} is now serving customers. The only place where the power to underpay your server is with YOU!</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_eatery2">{0} is open for business. The first restaurant to be staffed completely BY rats. </item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_eatery3">{0} is now open for business. Finally another chance to protest the unfair no shirt, no shoes, no service policy.</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_firstchurchofspringfield">First Church of Springfield has been built and Reverend Lovejoy is back. "Remember this second chance has been brought to you by God. Probably."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_generic1">{0} has finished building! Looks like trees have lost another battle.</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_generic2">{0} is complete! Forever people will think on this historic monument as a… place. </item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_home1">{0} has finished building. And the keys are right… oh no, where are the keys?!?</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_home2">{0} is complete! Don’t you just love that new house smell?</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_home3">{0} is done. Just a normal house with absolutely no murder basement.</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_krustyburger">Krusty Burger has been built and Krusty is back. "How can you rebuild society without fast food and corporate sponsors? Hyeh-yeh-yeh-yeh!"</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_krustyland1">{0} has just arrived in Krustyland!  Come to the only place where waiting in line is part of the fun!</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_krustyland2">{0} has just arrived in Krustyland! Home of childhood’s greatest traumas!</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_luigis">Luigi's has been built and Luigi is back. "It's a me! One of many racial stereotypes for when you get tired of old, yellow men."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_moestavern">Moe's Tavern has been built and Moe and Marge are both back. "Let's just say they were in Limbo… Heaven for one, Hell for the other."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_policestation">The Police Station has been built and Chief Wiggum is back. "This town is a lawless wasteland. Hope someone takes care of that soon."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_powerplant">Cooling Towers have been built and Mr. Burns is back. "Excellent! First I reestablish power in the town and then I will…reestablish power."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_shop1">{0} is now open for business. Finally selling the one thing that will finally bring you happiness.</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_shop2">{0} is now open! Bet you’re kicking yourself about forgetting your giant ribbon cutting scissors at home today.</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_shop3">{0} is open! Enjoy testing it out here and then buying it online for a lot less!</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_springfieldelementary">Springfield Elementary has been built and Skinner is back. "Ah, Springfield Elementary, and here I thought I'd just escaped Purgatory."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_springfieldlibrary">Springfield Library has been built and Martin is back. "Hark, it is the dawn of a new Springfield. And not a bully in sight!"</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_springfieldpenitentiary">Springfield Penitentiary has been built and Snake is back. "Aw riight! Now it's time to get out there in the wreckage and destroy some stuff!"</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_springfieldretirementcastle">Retirement Castle has been built and Grampa is back. "None of you even noticed I was gone this whole time! Nurse!"</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_townhall">Town Hall has been built and Mayor Quimby is back. "It will be an, ah, honor to serve as your mayor and to enjoy all the, ah, benefits thereof."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_twocharacter">{0} has been built. {1} and {2} are back.</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_vanhoutenhome">The Van Houten House has been built and Milhouse is back. "My house is empty and I'm alone. This new world seems an awful lot like the old one."</item>
    <item suffix="buildingcomplete_williesshack">Willie's Shack has been built and Willie is back. "Ach! Figures, a disaster flattens the town and you come running to the janitor!"</item>
    <item suffix="casino_gamblers">Gamblers are trying to go home. Tap them to send them back to the casino!</item>
    <item suffix="casino_maxgamblers24h">Gamblers are escaping their addiction. Tap them to drag them back in.</item>
    <item suffix="casino_playcasinogame">You haven’t gambled in a while. That means you’re due to win. Come play!</item>
    <item suffix="christmas_mysterystocking">LAST CHANCE to spend Santa Coins and get the limited time items! Got everything? Well check out the new Mystery Stocking!</item>
    <item suffix="comeback1week_alt">The Simpsons haven't seen you in a while, and are starting to wonder if you'll ever help rebuild Springfield.</item>
    <item suffix="comeback3day_alt">It's been a while,  you should see how your Springfield is doing.</item>
    <item suffix="crop_complete">Mmm… Crops.</item>
    <item suffix="crop_complete_alt">{0} are ready at {1}.</item>
    <item suffix="crop_plural">{0} are ready at {1}.</item>
    <item suffix="crop_singular">{0} is ready at {1}.</item>
    <item suffix="dailyplaycombopartone_complete">Come collect your daily Presents! 1 h left before you lose it.</item>
    <item suffix="dailyplaycomboparttwo_complete">Come collect your daily Elf Berries! 1 h left before you lose it.</item>
    <item suffix="dcs_challengelimit">You've reached your limit of available Daily Challenges! Make some room to keep those easy rewards rolling in!</item>
    <item suffix="dcs_newchallenge">A new Daily Challenge is available! It's not much of a challenge, but at least you get one every day!</item>
    <item suffix="decembertwentyfifth_complete">For the next 24 hours, the Tapped Out holiday event is…(insertbonus). Log in and check it out!</item>
    <item suffix="decembertwentyfirst_complete">This is your last chance to get an exclusive character for free! Hurry up to complete all daily challenges!</item>
    <item suffix="decembertwentysecond_complete">Apu's onto a Holiday Donut sale. Check in and see what he comes up with!</item>
    <item suffix="donutgiveawayearlyevent_complete">Thanks for joining the Clash of Clones! There's a little bonus waiting in your Springfield.</item>
    <item suffix="easter2014_bunniescomeback">Still buried in bunnies here! Log in and get those eggs!</item>
    <item suffix="easter2014_maxbunnies">Your Springfield is overrun. Log in to zap some bunnies!</item>
    <item suffix="eventending_complete">The Clash of Clones event will end soon! Get those last minute raids in before it's too late!</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_channel6_1">Channel 6 show’s over. You could get up to change the channel but we both know that’s not happening.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_channel6_2">Channel 6 show’s over. You can go back to conversing with your families now.  </item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_cletusfarm1">Crops are ready at Cletus’ Farm. Pick ‘em before the hipsters do.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_cletusfarm2">Crops are ready at Cletus’ Farm. Overall rentals are also available.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_cletusfarm3">Crops are ripe at Cletus’ Farm. Plus your friend the Scarecrow has been wondering when you’re coming back with that brain.  </item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_driveintheatre1">Drive-In movie is over. Remember any trash you leave behind will actually come with you.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_driveintheatre2">Drive-In movie is over.  And unlike a normal theater, you don’t even have to get up to leave.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_goldroad">A new gold road tile is ready to collect. Sure, you could have built more affordable housing, but bragging rights are so much cooler.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_kbblradio1">KBBL has finished their broadcast! Quick fill the air with fart sound effects – it’s what our listeners want.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_kbblradio2">KBBL has finished broadcasting a show. Put something else on fast or else the HAM radio people take over.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_openairstage1">An Open Air Stage show is finished. Now go ask them to produce your one-man show entitled Sadness.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_openairstage2">An Open Air Stage show has finished! Ah, the theater and clean oxygen: two things that the future won’t have!</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_squidport1">A new Squidport tile is ready to collect. Add one small piece for man, add one large piece for funnel cake sales.</item>
    <item suffix="farmcomplete_squidport2">A new Squidport tile is ready to collect. Finally give that offensive t-shirt shop a floor!</item>
    <item suffix="friend_visited">Visitors? Better put on some pants!</item>
    <item suffix="friend_visited_alt">{0} has visited your Springfield.</item>
    <item suffix="friendplacedsnake">{0} has released some snakes in your Springfield!</item>
    <item suffix="friendplacedsnakeegg">{0} has planted snake eggs in your Springfield!</item>
    <item suffix="gokarttrack_ready_alt">The Go-Kart Track is ready to race.</item>
    <item suffix="homergeddon_maxtappables">Ruffians have overwhelmed your town. Tap them into oblivion!</item>
    <item suffix="homergeddon_maxtappables_24hr">Ruffians have overrun your Springfield! Make room for more!</item>
    <item suffix="inactiveuser_2days">Hey, it's been 2 days, where have you been? If it was a hangover, Homer understands, just come back and we'll forget it ever happened.</item>
    <item suffix="inactiveuser_3days">Are you cheating on me with another game?</item>
    <item suffix="inactiveuser_3days_alt">It's been a while. You should see how your Springfield is doing.</item>
    <item suffix="inactiveuser_4days">Springfield has been cluttering up for 4 days! Without you, everyone is stuck with these 'thumbs up' icons over their heads. Come back and clean house!</item>
    <item suffix="inactiveuser_5days">You switched to Tiny Tower, didn't you?</item>
    <item suffix="inactiveuser_5days_alt">The Simpsons haven't seen you in a while and are starting to wonder if you'll ever help rebuild Springfield</item>
    <item suffix="inactiveuser_7days">7 days and Springfield hasn't changed a bit. Help us, Sky Finger, you're our only hope!</item>
    <item suffix="inactiveuser_14days">Hey there, neighborino! Not to be a Nagging Nelly here, but it's been 14 days since you stopped rebuilding our town and we really need you back.</item>
    <item suffix="job_complete">Quittin' Time!</item>
    <item suffix="job_complete_alt">{0} has finished {1}.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_apu1">Apu has finished his job. He would have gotten it done faster if he was legally allowed to work a 26-hour day.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_apu2">Apu has finished his job. Not even Ganesh with his many arms could have done it faster.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_bart">Bart has finished a job! Now to cover his tracks and create an alibi. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_bart_haveasleepover">Bart’s Have a Sleepover is done! Now Milhouse has to get his bra out from the freezer.  Maybe then he’ll tell us why he was wearing a bra in the first place. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_bart_skateboard">Bart has finished Skateboarding! He did so much that he competed in the X games as well as the Y and Z games. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_burns1">Mr. Burns has completed a job! Well, in all likelihood it was one of his indentured servants who did it…</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_burns2">Mr. Burns has completed a job! Let's just hope that it hasn't led to the summoning of another demon this time.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_burns3">Mr. Burns has completed a job! And this time without a single human sacrifice!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_cbguy1">Comic Book Guy has completed a job! He keeps his paychecks in their original envelopes to increase their value.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_cbguy2">Comic Book Guy has completed a job! Sure the job was originally intended for a child but now it’s a collectible job. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_cletus1">Cletus has completed a job! Which is a sentence I never thought I'd have to write…</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_cletus2">Cletus has completed a job! And he’s placed an X by it. Two more X’s and he’ll be drunk!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_cletus3">Cletus has completed a job! Now if only they paid him more than his trained raccoon co-workers.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_generic1">{0} has finished a job. Better assign something else to them before they can start asking questions about their existence. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_generic2">{0} has finished a job. It’s a perfect time to steal all their money and XP! </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_generic3">{0}'s job is done! Quick give them a new one before they can unionize. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_grampa1">Grampa has completed a job! And he wants to tell you all about it. It started on a steamboat on the Mighty Mississippi way back in 1942.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_grampa2">Grampa has completed a job! Unlike all those good-for-nothing hippies.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_grampa3">Grampa has completed a job! And got it done in time for Matlock.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_homer1">Homer has finished a job! Or rather, the monkey he trained has finished it.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_homer2">Homer has finished a job! For the first time ever!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_homer3">Homer has finished a job! But just don’t check his work because it’s definitely done. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_homer_drinkatmoes1">Homer has finished Drink at Moe’s. Kicked out, finished – what’s the difference really?</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_homer_drinkatmoes2">Homer has finished Drink at Moe’s. Oh we meant finished all the drinks at Moe’s. Moe has to restock.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_homer_monkeytraumacenter">Homer is done Watching Monkey Trauma Center Marathon! He watched all that TV without a snack – give that man a trophy!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_krusty1">Krusty has completed a job! Just don't tell the IRS. He really doesn't want to have to pay taxes on it.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_krusty2">Krusty has completed a job! Well actually Sideshow Mel did but Krusty is taking all the credit.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_lisa1">Lisa has finished a job! Now give her a gold star, so she can stop hyperventilating.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_lisa2">Lisa has finished a job! She expects a grade and that grade better be an A… or else.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_lisa_playthesax">Lisa has finished Play the Sax. Give the neighbors anything but the blues by assigning her to something else. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_lisa_shopatkwikemart">Lisa has finished Shop at Kwik-E-Mart! She thought they were carrying kale chips but it turned out they were just shriveled napkins.  </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_lovejoy1">Reverend Lovejoy has completed a job! If his next job isn’t train related, he’s quitting God.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_lovejoy2">Reverend Lovejoy has completed a job! Which is a miracle, considering how many calls he got from Ned. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_luigi1">Luigi has completed a job! And it's given all of Springfield indigestion.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_luigi2">Luigi has completed a job! Call Guinness, I think he broke the record for world's greasiest Stromboli.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_marge"> Marge has finished a job! Now on to the next underappreciated menial task!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_marge_protestsomething1">Marge has finished Protest… Something! Just in time to protest something else!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_marge_protestsomething2">Marge has finished Protest… Something! She likes the causes but loves crafting the signs!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_marge_visitjakesunisex1">Marge’s Visit Jake’s Unisex Hair Palace is done! It takes two stylists, one ladder and so much blue dye to get that look.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_marge_visitjakesunisex2">Marge’s Visit Jake’s Unisex Hair Palace is done! Now quick, compliment her hair before something bad happens. </item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_martin1">Martin has completed a job! Next it looks like the bullies are going to make him complete their jobs too.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_martin2">Martin has completed a job! No one asked him to do it, no one wanted him to do it, but he did it anyway.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_milhouse1">Milhouse has completed a job! Which is adorable if you think about it. Good for him.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_milhouse2">Milhouse has completed a job! Do you think Lisa will notice?</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_moe1">Moe has completed a job! The world always has use for the rude, creepy, and unpleasant.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_moe2">Moe has completed a job! Next time he’d love a job that doesn’t require him to wear a mask.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_moe3">Moe has completed a job! Another few bucks for the plastic surgery fund!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_ned1">Ned has completed a job! Now if only hard work weren't a sin for some reason…</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_ned2">Ned has completed a job! Now he just needs to check in with Reverend Lovejoy to make sure he did it without accidentally sinning.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_ned3">Ned has completed a job! And he did it using only his left hand.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_quimby1">Mayor Quimby has completed a job! Just don't tell anyone about it. Rigging an election is supposed to stay secret.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_quimby2">Mayor Quimby completed a job! Say what you want: judging the Miss Springfield Pageant is still work.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_quimby3">Mayor Quimby has completed a job! Now to take his well-deserved, two-month Bahamas vacation on the tax payers dime.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_skinner1">Skinner has completed a job! And he did it with the unbridled passion and exactitude of the Amish.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_skinner2">Skinner has completed a job! Which was necessary. That principal salary can't pay all the bills.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_skinner3">Skinner has completed a job! And by the end of it, the job was bored of Skinner.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_snake1">Snake has completed a job! About time, too. He's been casing the place for months.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_snake2">Snake has completed a job! And Apu only got shot three times during it!</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_snake3">Snake has completed a job! Now all he needs to do is find a place to fence the art.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_wiggum1">Chief Wiggum has completed a job! And he only took four lunch breaks during it.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_wiggum2">Chief Wiggum has completed a job! Now to celebrate by shooting his gun into the air… oh no, where’s his gun?</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_wiggum3">Chief Wiggum has completed a job! Now let’s never make him work again.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_willie1">Willie has completed a job! And he can't believe they made him do it during Skotchtober Fest.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_willie2">Willie has completed a job! Now he finally can go back to his precious shack for some peace and quiet.</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_willie3">Willie has completed a job! But mind your own business, what's it to you??</item>
    <item suffix="jobcomplete_willie4">Willie has completed a job! Work as hard as you want, Willie. You'll never be able to hide from the specter of an ever-approaching death.</item>
    <item suffix="june2015_droptheball">{0} has thrown a ball into your town!</item>
    <item suffix="june2015_maxfans">Your town is full for sports fans. Sell them some merchandise!</item>
    <item suffix="june2015_newchallenges">New challenges available. Complete them for a Tap Ball reward.</item>
    <item suffix="june2015_playedopponent">Your tap ball team has played a game while you were gone. Log in and see how they did!</item>
    <item suffix="labordaydonuts2012_na">Download the latest update of Tapped Out this weekend.  We'll give you a dozen donuts if you do!</item>
    <item suffix="labordaydonuts2012_na_alt">Enjoy Labor Day weekend by staying inside and playing Tapped Out… with a dozen FREE DONUTS!</item>
    <item suffix="labordaydonuts2012_na_alt2">Download the update and enjoy Labor Day weekend by staying inside and playing Tapped Out… with a dozen FREE DONUTS!</item>
    <item suffix="labordaydonuts2012_row">Celebrate the the end of summer by staying inside and playing Tapped Out… with a dozen FREE DONUTS!</item>
    <item suffix="labordaydonuts2012_row_alt">Download the update to celebrate the the end of summer by staying inside and playing Tapped Out… with a dozen FREE DONUTS!</item>
    <item suffix="lemontree_stolen">I was gonna make lemonade.</item>
    <item suffix="lemontree_stolen_alt">The lemon tree is gone!</item>
    <item suffix="maxsnakes">Springfield is overrun with snakes. Better get whacking!</item>
    <item suffix="maxsnakes24hours">Snakes are all over your Springfield, just begging to be whacked!</item>
    <item suffix="medieval_buildingwrecked_complete">%FRIEND% is raiding your town!</item>
    <item suffix="medieval_lastchance">The Clash of Clones event will end soon! Get those last minute raids in before it's too late!</item>
    <item suffix="medieval_loginreminder_complete">Who's defending your Springfield?</item>
    <item suffix="medieval_maxtroops_complete">Your army awaits! Invade other Springfields to earn more Elixir and Gold!</item>
    <item suffix="medieval_trooprush_complete">A new wave of suicidal nerds has entered Springfield. You now have a full army!</item>
    <item suffix="medieval_wednesday_complete">Does your castle need a little boost? Elixir packs are available in the store for a limited time.</item>
    <item suffix="minigameready_sideshowyou1">Sideshow You is ready to play! If you win a big stuffed animal, your chances of getting a girlfriend go up 45%!</item>
    <item suffix="minigameready_sideshowyou2">Sideshow You is ready to play! Unpop some big prizes and bonus points if the dart hits the carnie.</item>
    <item suffix="moesark_frienddeployedinvasivetoad">You have been bamboozled by ${FRIEND}! Clear that Invasive Toad!</item>
    <item suffix="moesark_maxtappables">Zoo Visitors have swarmed your town. Tap them into oblivion!</item>
    <item suffix="moesark_maxtappables_24hr">Zoo Visitors have overrun your Springfield! Make room for more!</item>
    <item suffix="monorail_eventendthreedays">Event ends in 3 days. Make sure you get the current prizes before it's too late!</item>
    <item suffix="monorail_friendaction">Do you smell something? %Friend Name% has dumped Garbage in your town!</item>
    <item suffix="monorail_newprizetrack">Throw up your hands and raise your voice! New Monorail prizes available!</item>
    <item suffix="monorail_newprojects">Back to work! Daily Challenge now available, earn extra rewards and unlock Monorail prizes!</item>
    <item suffix="monorail_prizetrackendthreedays">New prizes coming in 3 days. Make sure you get the current prizes before it's too late!</item>
    <item suffix="music_frienddeployedlawyer">You have been served by ${FRIEND}! Clear that lawyer!</item>
    <item suffix="music_maxfans">Festival Fans have overwhelmed your town. Tap them to send them packing!</item>
    <item suffix="music_maxfans24h">Festival Fans have overrun your Springfield! Make room more!</item>
    <item suffix="newprizetrackavailable_complete">Brand new prizes are on offer! Come play the Christmas 2014 update and squish some elves!</item>
    <item suffix="playertownfullelves_complete">Your town is full of mischievous elves. Tap them to bottle them!</item>
    <item suffix="playertownhasagents_complete">Your friends have sent the Feds to your Springfield. Thwart them to earn some Elf Berries!</item>
    <item suffix="prizetrackpartoneendingthreedays_complete">Have you got all your prizes yet? Now's your last chance! New prizes coming soon!</item>
    <item suffix="prizetrackpartoneendingtwodays_complete">2 days left before Part 1 ends. Hurry up and complete all the challenges to get an exclusive character!</item>
    <item suffix="prizetrackparttwoendingthreedays_complete">Have you got all your prizes yet? Now's your last chance! Part 2 will end soon!</item>
    <item suffix="prizetrackparttwoendingtwodays_complete">2 days left before Part 2 ends. Hurry up and collect enough Elf Berries to unlock all the prizes!</item>
    <item suffix="railyard24hrwarning">Only 1 day left to earn this week's Rail Yard prizes! Hit the job board and win big before they are gone!</item>
    <item suffix="railyard_newprizes">This week's prizes are available at the Rail Yard! Get 'em while they're hot!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_3daysremain">Only 3 days remain before this event concludes! Make sure to get your prizes while you can.</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_act2start">New prizes and Sci-Fi stories await you in Springfield!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_act3start">A huge new enemy robot is menacing Springfield. Come back to deal with this threat!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_anne1">LadyBot is available in the store. Find out how Frink's robotic creation yearns for the outside world.</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_anne2">LadyBot is available in the store. Find out how Frink's robotic creation yearns for the outside world.</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_bigdigiben">Need to know the time, but don't want to look at your clock? Big Digi-Ben can help!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_elysium">Want to bring a high-tech Garden of Eden to Springfield, and party in it? Pick it up in the store now!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_futuremonument">The future monument is available in the store. What's up with that?</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_giantrobots">What's a robot update without gigantic robots? Pick them up in the store now!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_holosuite">A collection of holographic items is now available in the store.</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_maxrobots">Robots are invading Springfield! Come smash them up now!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_maxrobots24h">Come back! Springfield needs you to beat back those vile robots!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_playscifighter">SciFighter is ready for use.</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_rockettoyourdoom">The Rocket to your Doom is now available for purchase in the store.</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_soulextractioninstitute">The future of burns, and his little puppy dog too! Available now in the store!</item>
    <item suffix="scifi_worldoftomorrowsign">A holographic sign to proudly identify your Springfield's Future District is now available.</item>
    <item suffix="scratchr_ready">Another Scratch-R ticket is ready to buy! Come in and see what you've won!</item>
    <item suffix="season24prem27sept_na">The Simpsons 24th season begins this Sunday. Play now to receive a free gift to celebrate.</item>
    <item suffix="season24prem27sept_row">We’re giving away a Duff Racer from the Springfield Grand Prix. Play now to receive your free gift.</item>
    <item suffix="season24prem30sept_na">Last chance to get a free gift to celebrate tonight’s Simpsons 24th season premiere.</item>
    <item suffix="season24prem30sept_row">Last chance to get your Duff Racer from the Springfield Grand Prix.</item>
    <item suffix="secretagents_dossier5h">Oh no! Time's running out on a dossier. Better hurry!</item>
    <item suffix="secretagents_dossier24h">Enemy agencies have free reign of your Springfield. Are you really going to let them monitor your browsing history?</item>
    <item suffix="secretagents_friend">{0} has hacked your Springfield WiFi! Stop them from stealing your bandwidth!</item>
    <item suffix="secretagents_manintan">Men-in-Tan have overwhelmed your town. Tap them to send them packing!</item>
    <item suffix="sideshowbob_active">Don't kill me, kill the boy!</item>
    <item suffix="sideshowbob_active_alt">Sideshow Bob has escaped from Prison!</item>
    <item suffix="sideshowbob_captured_alt">Sideshow Bob has been apprehended by {0}.</item>
    <item suffix="sideshowbob_caught">Bus-ted!</item>
    <item suffix="springfielddowns_ready">Doo-do-do-doo doo-do-do-doo doo doo doo doo!</item>
    <item suffix="springfielddowns_ready1">There’s a new race ready to start at Springfield Downs! Come in and make some questionable decisions!</item>
    <item suffix="springfielddowns_ready2">There’s a new race ready to start at Springfield Downs! Because what’s the point of being a winner if no one bet on you?</item>
    <item suffix="springfielddowns_ready_alt">Springfields Downs is ready to race.</item>
    <item suffix="springfieldjobs_frienddeployedcrook">You have been bamboozled by ${FRIEND}! Clear that crook!</item>
    <item suffix="springfieldjobs_maxtappables">Justice Agents have swarmed your town. Tap them into oblivion!</item>
    <item suffix="springfieldjobs_maxtappables_24hr">Justice Agents have overrun your Springfield! Make room for more!</item>
    <item suffix="stonecutters_robedfigures">The Order has sent spies to your Springfield. Thwart them to earn some Emblems!</item>
    <item suffix="stonecutters_robedfigures24hours">These robed figures are up to no good, stop them to earn some Emblems!</item>
    <item suffix="stonecutters_sacredparchment">A new prophecy has been revealed! Can you solve the puzzle to earn prizes and Emblems?</item>
    <item suffix="stonecutters_spy">Quick! %FriendName% is spying on your Springfield foil their evil plot and earn Emblems!</item>
    <item suffix="stonecutters_spykl">Quick! %FriendName% is spying on your Krustyland foil their evil plot and earn Emblems!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes2_felon24h">We need you now to stop these wandering Felons!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes2_felonspawn">Come back and teach these Felons a good lesson! Springfield needs you!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes2_maxcriminals">Crime is running rampant in Springfield! Capture Criminals and take a chomp out of crime!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes2_maxcriminals24h">We're holding out for a hero! Come rid Springfield of Criminals!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes_friendcrimereport">Hurry! %FriendName% has reported a crime in your Springfield! Respond quicker than Springfield PD for more rewards!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes_maxcriminals">Crime is running rampant in Springfield!  Capture them and take a chomp out of crime!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes_maxcriminalsreminder">We're holding out for a hero! Come rid Springfield of Criminals!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes_teaserfinalchapter">Only 3 days before the super saga concludes. Make sure to get your prizes while you can!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes_unlockchapter">New prizes available for heroes brave enough to fight back the crime in Springfield!</item>
    <item suffix="superheroes_unlockfinalchapter">Pay your respects to Radioactive Man, but be on your guard… it’s dangerous out there!</item>
    <item suffix="terwilligers_24hrsmaxmutants">Your town is overflowing with Mutants. Gross.</item>
    <item suffix="terwilligers_frienddeployedseedling">Hurry! %FRIEND% has seeded your town with Mutants! Harvest them quickly for extra resources!</item>
    <item suffix="terwilligers_maxmutantclones">Bob Clones are swarming your town. Get rid of them and harvest those resources!</item>
    <item suffix="terwilligers_maxmutantplants">Mutant Plants are growing all over your town. Reap them to reap rewards.</item>
    <item suffix="themepark2018_maxtappables">Park Visitors are shoulder to shoulder. Make some room!</item>
    <item suffix="themepark2018_maxtappables_24hr">Park Visitors have overrun your Springfield! Make room for more!</item>
    <item suffix="thespiritofgiving">Enjoy the Holidays with 25% more donuts in every package!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2013_ghostscomeback">Ghosts are terrorizing your Springfield, think of the children.</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2013_gremlinsexpired">It's been 4 hours since you released your Gremlins off. Log in to see their GOO haul!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2013_gremlinssquished">{0} has squished one of your Gremlins! Oh no!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2013_maxghosts">Springfield is overrun with ghosts! It's time to get popping!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2014_finalprizetrackending">Have you got all your prizes yet? Now's your last chance!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2014_gremalienexpired">It's been 4 hours since you released your Grem-Aliens. Log in to see their haul!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2014_gremaliensquished">%FRIEND% has squished one of your Grem-Aliens. Oh dear!​</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2014_maxrigellians">Springfield is overrun with Rigellian Invaders. It's time to teach them a lesson they won't forget.</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2014_prizetrackavailable">Brand new prizes are on offer! Come play the Treehouse of Horror update and squish some aliens!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2014_prizetrackending">Have you got all your prizes yet? Now's your last chance! New prizes coming soon!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2014_rigellianscomeback">Rigellians are invading your Springfield! Think of the children!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2015_backtotheskies">M'nthster has risen and is now terrorizing Springfield. Stop this madness!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2015_campfirebeatdownwillfail">M'nthster is almost ready to takeoff and spread hysteria again. Throw Christmas Junk at him before it's too late!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2015_formlessterrordeployed">Hurry! %FRIEND% has unleashed Formless Terrors upon your town. Expel them for extra resources!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2015_newchallenges">New challenges await! Finish all of them in time for a special bonus prize!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2015_nightmaresmax">Nightmares are spreading rapidly across Springfield! Get in there and save the town from madness.</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2015_nightmaresmax24hr">Springfield has been devoured by madness! Help pull the town out of this nightmare.</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2015_starspawnmax">Servants of M'nthster are flooding your town. Rid Springfield of the dreaded Star Spawn!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2017_maxtappables">Mystical Pests have overwhelmed your town. Tap them to banish them!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2017_maxtappables_24hr">Mystical Pests have overrun your Springfield! Make room for more!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2018_maxtappables">Monster Minions are filling your town. Make some room!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh2018_maxtappables_24hr">Monster Minions have overrun your Springfield! Make room for more!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh_friendvisited">{0} has just trashed {1}!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh_maxhumanzombies">There's a massive hoard of zombies roaming Springfield!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh_maxpetzombies">Springfield is raining zombie cats and dogs!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh_maxzombiesreminder">What, have you been turned into a Zombie  too?  Save your Springfield!</item>
    <item suffix="thoh_simpsonscharacterzombified">{0} has turned into a zombie!</item>
    <item suffix="ttt_maxtappables">Time Travellers fill Springfield! Time to get medieval on them!</item>
    <item suffix="ttt_maxtappables_24h">Time Travellers are running wild all over Springfield! Come and tap them!</item>
    <item suffix="wday_comeback">Snakes are all over your Springfield, just begging to be whacked!</item>
    <item suffix="wday_maxsnakes">Springfield is overrun with snakes. Better get Whacking!</item>
    <item suffix="wday_snakesreleased">{0} has sneaked into your Springfield and released some snakes!</item>
    <item suffix="wildwest_banditmax">Springfield is crawling with Bandits. Round them up now!</item>
    <item suffix="wildwest_banditmax24hr">Bandits control Springfield. Come to the rescue!</item>
    <item suffix="wildwest_newwantedbandit">You got the guts to take down the Wanted Bandit?</item>
    <item suffix="wildwest_newwantedbandit24hr">A huge Bandit is rampaging through town! Stop him!</item>
    <item suffix="wildwest_treasurehunterdeployed">A no-good Prospector is searching for gold in town!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2013_comeback">We're holding out for a hero! Come rid Springfield of Criminals!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2013_frienddroppedgiftbag">Your friends have dropped a bunch of Gift Bags in your Springfield! Log in to see what you got.</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2013_maxpresents">Crime is running rampant in Springfield!  Capture them and take a chomp out of crime!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2014_dailycombopart1">Come collect your daily reward! 1h left before you lose it.</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2014_dailycombopart2">Come collect your daily reward! 1h left before you lose it.</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2014_federalagents">Your friends have sent the Feds to your Springfield. Thwart them to earn some Presents!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2014_maxelves">Your town is full of mischievous elves! Tap them to bottle them!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2015_dropapresent">{0} has dropped a present in your Springfield. Respond now to collect your rewards!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2015_maxbears">Your town is full of bears. Get in there and send them back to their cave! </item>
    <item suffix="xmas2015_maxbears24h">The bears are missing their cave. Get in there and tap them!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2015_maxmerrymakers">Your town is full of merrymakers. Give them a taste of that new festive Squishee! </item>
    <item suffix="xmas2015_maxmerrymakers24h">The merrymakers are waiting for their daily Squishee. Get in there and tap them!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2015_minigameready">Maggie's eager to play hide and seek with you. Don't let her down!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2015_newchallenges">New challenges await! Finish all of them in time for a special bonus prize!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2017_bossbattle">You dealt another blow! Continue fighting to save Christmas!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2017_maxtappables">Robo-Funzos have taken your town. Tap them to send them packing!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2017_maxtappables_24hr">Springfield is swarmed with Robo-Funzos. Destroy them all!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas2017_presentblaster">The Present Blaster is ready to blast!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas_decoratedhouses">Collect Santa Coins from your houses now!</item>
    <item suffix="xmas_holidaytree">Your holiday tree is ready! Collect your Santa Coins now!</item>
    <item suffix="xpcollider_complete">The XP Collider just shut down. Come back to recharge it to maintain your x5 XP Boost!</item>
    <item suffix="xpcollider_nearcomplete">The XP Collider will shut down in 2 hours. Don't forget to recharge it to maintain your x5 XP Boost!</item>
  </group>
</sbtp>